50millionpounds.com 2012-01-17

# Privacy Policy

| 

The 50 Million Pound Challenge ("we" or "us") recognizes the importance of respecting the privacy of those who visit this web site and choose to take advantage of the programs and information offered by us at this site. This General Privacy Policy provides an overview of what you can expect when you enroll in our program or simply browse our site.

The 50 Million Pound Challenge collects personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") at this site only when you provide the information to us, such as when you choose to enroll the Challenge program, online contests, sweepstakes, or other programs offered through this site. 

## Why Does The 50 Million Pound Challenge Collect Personal Information?

We collect personal information for the following reasons:

  1. To provide you with the products or services you have requested; 
  2. To better understand you, to allow us to serve you better through enhanced products, customer service and directed promotional efforts of particular interest; 
  3. To properly investigate and respond to any complaints, questions or concerns you may have about our products or services; and 
  4. To determine your eligibility for our products and services.
  5. If you opt in to receive offers, promotions or other information from The 50 Million Pound Challenge, your information will be used to provide you with promotional offers for the products that we believe may interest you and to solicit your opinion on our products and services. If you have opted in to receive these offers, we may also use your personal information to ensure that your contact information is accurate and up to date. 

How the information is used:

  * The information is used to enhance the visitor's experience when using the website to display personalized content and possibly advertising.
  * We do not sell member information.
  * We do not allow those who are doing business on our behalf to use our member information for their own marketing purposes.
  * We contractually require any person or organization providing products or services on our behalf to protect The 50 Million Pound Challenge member information.
  * We do not share member medical information with anyone within The 50 Million Pound Challenge organization, affiliates, or subsidiaries, unless: 
    * You expressly authorize it.
    * It is permitted or required by law.
  * We afford our prospective and former members the same protections as existing members with respect to the use of personal information.

We do not collect Personal Information in connection with "browsing" our web site. However, our servers automatically collect aggregate information about your use of our site when you visit and browse the site ("Site Use Information"). The Site Use Information includes but is not limited to the following: the domain names, operating system in use (e.g., Macintosh, Windows), browser (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer) and version, the web site that referred you to us, and other similar information. This information may be aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on our site, pages viewed, time and date of visits, and other similar information. We may use and disclose Site Use Information, for example, to measure the use of our site, explain the utility of our site, and to improve the content of our site. 

We also make use of "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a small piece of data that our web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer. One of the ways we use cookies is to identify computers that are being used to make visits to our web site. We also may customize, monitor, or regulate the use of our site based on information stored in the cookie or host server. In addition, we use session cookies to recognize the user when moving from page to page in our site. By using this site, you consent to the use of our cookies. 

Please note that if you enter our web site from another web site, it is possible that the other site may use cookies to learn of your visit to our web site. We have no control over cookies used by other sites. 

We do not use any of our online sites or services to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. 

We reserve the right to change or supplement our privacy policies at any time by posting the changes on this web site. By using this web site, you accept the terms and conditions of this privacy policy, and you agree to review this privacy policy from time to time to stay informed of changes that may occur.   
  
---|---
